https://www.chcweb.com/catalog/ordering_policy.html

0 Items
Home > Ordering & Policies
Ordering InformationShipping Information Return PolicySecure ShoppingPrivacy PolicyPermissions and Copyright
Ordering Information
Thank you for your interest in CHC materials! There are several options available for placing an order.
Online Orders may be placed online 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Click here to enter our secure online store. You may also browse our paper catalog online here.
Toll Free Call 1-800-490-7713 toll free from anywhere within the U.S. and Canada. Our phone representatives are available to help you place your order on Monday through Friday. Please have your credit card information handy.
Fax Fax your order, along with your credit card information, to: 1-972-502-9203.
Mail You may mail your order to:
Catholic Heritage Curricula4020 N. MacArthur Blvd., Ste. 122-320Irving, TX 75038
We can accept payment by check and money order as well as Visa, MasterCard, and Discover Card. All prices listed on this website are in U.S. Funds. Prices are subject to change without notice. Click here to download a printable order form.
Shipping Information
Our goal is to ship your order within 24 hours. We ship via United Parcel Service (UPS) and United States Postal Service (USPS). If you are a registered user, you may quickly and easily track your shipments. Click here.
Shipping Chart: U.S.
Order Subtotal
Media Mail* (2-21 days)
Priority Mail** (1-4 days)
UPS Ground*** (1-5 days)
Express**** (2 business days)
$0 - $15.00
$4.95
$7.95
$15.75
$34.95
$15.01 - $25.00
$5.75
$9.75
35%
* MEDIA MAIL: Economical, tracked shipping method. Delivery time reliably runs 2-8 business days, but can take up to 21 business days. ** PRIORITY MAIL: Delivery within 1-4 business days, depending on location. *** UPS GROUND: Tracked and reliable delivery within 1-5 business days, depending on location. Please supply a street address for UPS delivery. **** EXPRESS: UPS 2nd Day Air. Due to COVID-19, UPS is no longer guaranteeing timely delivery, so we have temporarily discontinued the Express rate.
Shipping Chart: Canada
Order Subtotal
Priority Mail International or First Class* (6-20 days, delivery fees not pre-paid)
$0 - $15.00
$17.99
$15.01 - $25.00
$21.99
$25.01 - $40.00
$28.75
$40.01 - $55.00
$33.50
29%
* Customer is responsible for all taxes, customs, and duties.
Shipping Chart: Other International
COVID-19 UPDATE: Due to postal delays and service disruptions in many countries, Catholic Heritage Curricula has suspended direct shipment to international addresses except to Canada. Customers with order destinations other than the U.S. or Canada can order by using a mail forwarding service such as www.myus.com. Other options include addresspal.anpost.ie (Ireland) and lbcexpress.com (Philippines).
Order Subtotal
Priority Mail International*
$0 - $30.00
$55.00
$30.01 - $55.00
$65.00
$55.01 - $75.00
$75.00
$75.01 - $150.00
$80.00
$150.01 - $200.00
$85.00
$200.01+
45%
* PRIORITY MAIL INTERNATIONAL: Estimated shipping time is 10-14 business days for Priority Mail International shipments. Catholic Heritage Curricula reserves the right to refuse to ship to countries with unreliable postal systems, at our discretion. Catholic Heritage Curricula is not responsible for international shipments, and we will not replace orders that are lost or damaged. Upon delivery, the customer is responsible for any taxes, customs, or duties which may be imposed by the destination country.
Shipping Chart: AK, HI, APO, FPO
Order Subtotal
Media Mail*
Priority Mail**
$0 - $15.00
$4.95
$7.95
$15.01 - $25.00
15%
* MEDIA MAIL: Economical, tracked shipping method. Delivery can take up to 21 business days. ** PRIORITY MAIL: Alaska/Hawaii estimated shipping time is 1-3 business days; APO/FPO estimated shipping
time is 7-13 business days.
Return Policy
Please check your order as soon as it arrives. If you receive the wrong item or the material is defective, please contact us within 14 days of receipt of your order for a prompt and hassle-free replacement. Report discrepancies here.
If you are not satisfied with an item, please visit www.chcweb.com/catalog/return.html to obtain a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number and the return address. Books must be in new, unused condition to qualify for a refund. As soon as your return arrives, you will be issued a prompt refund of the cost of the books minus a 15% restocking fee. No returns accepted after 60 days; returns must be postmarked within 60 days of the order date to receive a refund.
Please be sure to use the return shipping address provided during the RMA process; returns must be shipped to our Ohio distribution center to receive a refund.
Final Sale Items: Loose-leaf books, lesson plans, tear-off pads, art cards/prints, DVDs, CDs, e-books, Bargain Basement titles, and Limited Quantity titles are final sale items; no returns are accepted. Loose-leaf books and tear-off pads are noted as such in the product description.
CHC is a family-owned and operated apostolate/business; we appreciate your cooperation with the return policy so that our work of publishing and providing Catholic materials for your family may continue. Thank you!
SECURE SHOPPING
You can shop at www.chcweb.com with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to accept credit card payments safely and securely for our customers.
The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card processing networks. The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including:
128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions.
Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information.
Compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS).
For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.Net Privacy Policy.
www.chcweb.com is registered with the Authorize.Net Verified Merchant Seal program.
PRIVACY POLICY
Catholic Heritage Curricula does not share, sell, rent, or give away our customers' personal information, other than what is necessary to process and fill orders.  We do not store individual credit card information for any reason.  We do not sell or rent our customers' email addresses; for customers to receive "Educating for Eternity E-newsletter" they must subscribe.
For questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us by mail:
Catholic Heritage Curricula4020 N. MacArthur Blvd., Ste. 122-320Irving, TX 75038
Or email:  chc@chcweb.com
Permissions and Copyright
All requests to reproduce material published by CHC must be made in writing.
Please submit your inquiries in writing to: Catholic Heritage Curricula, Attn: RoseMary Johnson, 4020 N. MacArthur Blvd., Ste. 122-320, Irving, TX 75038
You may also fax your request to: (972) 502-9203.
Home | Contact | FAQ | Catalog Request | Wish List | Ordering & Policies | Online Catalog | Support | Exclusives
© 2020 Catholic Heritage Curricula
